G-Girlfriend...
She's my girlfriend!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Mizuhara Chizuru.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Rental Girlfriend
"The End of the Girlfriend"
Wait, huh? Where's my phone?
Oh, I'm sorry. I must've dropped it.
Uh, that "rental girlfriend" just now?
Why'd it look like Chizuru-san?
Chizuru-san's a rental girlfriend?
Wow, is that true?
Th-That was a shopped image!
We made that as a joke some time ago!
Shopped...
...image?
Rental Girlfriend
W-Wait, that's the actual website.
So it's true, then?
R-Rental girlfriend means
what I think it means, right?
You go around pretending
to be your client's girlfriend?
Are you working that job, Chizuru-san?
Wha...
Wha... Wha...
What? No way.
The secret's out?
That Mizuhara's a rental girlfriend?
Now, of all times? In front of everybody?
What's gonna happen now?
Mizuhara can neither admit
nor deny it in this situation!
What do we do about this?
We're talking rental girlfriend here!
It's not like she's waitressing at a café!
They're not gonna hear she's
working that job and go, "Oh, okay."
It says you're number one.
That's impressive.
Have you been doing this long?
And Mami's attempt to cover it up
only made things worse!
This is what you call
a real sticky situation!
Calm down, man.
They haven't found out about us yet.
Hold up. Did you know
about this, Kazu-chin?
I gotta brush it off.
O-Of course I did.
Don't let it show. Don't let it show!
Well, did it work? Did they buy it?
Crap, I can't look any of them in the eye!
Let's go, Chizuru.
Mizuhara's totally panicking, too.
We can't stay here!
We gotta brush it off
and act like it's nothing!
Money.
Huh?
That money.
Huh?!
I saw you handing her a bunch
of cash outside your apartment.
Dad!
Right, he did see me giving her money!
What money?
I saw a handover of money
between Kazuya and Chizuru-san.
Why didn't you mention that, dear?
I thought Kazuya was in debt!
I told him to talk to me if he was.
Wait. Does that mean the two of them...
This is not good.
They're not going to stop.
The truth really will get out.
Crap... I'm getting dizzy.
I'm blacking out.
Why now? Why here?
I was all ready to put an end to it
once we were back in Tokyo.
Please.
God... Buddha... anyone will do!
Please just stop this now!
I'm sorry, you two.
Mami-chan?
I want you to be happy.
I'd never do anything to ruin your life.
I... I...
I can't cover it up anymore!
Cover it up?
Then it's true?
We're screwed. It's over.
There's no way I can explain
the money thing away.
And Mami-chan seems like she's
ready to tell them everything!
Everything around me is fading out.
My whole world's turning upside-down.
It's over. It's all over.
We're busted.
They know Mizuhara's a rental
girlfriend, and not my real girlfriend.
My brain can't process all this!
My mind's going blank!
What's going on?
They're talking about
rental girlfriends or something.
Now everyone else is catching on, too.
Duh. Our group's just
standing around talking.
What about Kibe? Mom and Dad?
What are they thinking?
Why isn't Gran saying anything?
Is she so angry that she froze up?
Or is she so sad that
she's lost for words?
Or has she just lost all hope in me?
I have no idea what's coming.
This is a total disaster!
Wait, everyone.
Kazuya.
I want to hear it from you.
Is Chizuru-san a rental girlfriend?
Is she not really your girlfriend, then?
What the hell? Why are you
looking at me like that?
Why are you so calm about this?
No... I can't find the words!
After a year and a half,
I'd finally stopped thinking...
that she was too perfect
to be your girlfriend.
I see.
I see now.
I can't do anything but apologize.
I gotta get on my knees
right here and now,
and I gotta tell her everything,
even if she beats me black and blue.
And I gotta say it's all my fault!
That's the only thing I can do now.
I-I'm sor—
I'm so sorry, Chizuru-san!
It's all my fault!
Is Mami-chan trying to help us out?
You told me to keep quiet, and yet...
What? Keep quiet?
Chizuru-san said that?
Mami-san?!
I can't, Chizuru-san!
I can't deal with this anymore!
I'm sorry for not telling you sooner,
Granny Nagomi!
I tried so many times!
I told them to stop doing this
because I felt so bad for your family!
Wait, what?
I told them to stop leading you on!
I knew Kazuya-san was paying money, too!
I just couldn't bear to see it!
What?!
I heard she even took
your family's prized ring.
And he spent all his
college spending money.
He even started working part-time
to rent Chizuru-san out!
What are you doing, Mami-chan?
I told her over and over and over again!
But she just wouldn't listen!
She thinks she can get away with anything
by saying she was being a professional!
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
You're making it sound like she's the...
But this is just too much!
She did this knowing that
Nagomi-san wanted a successor!
Even though she had no
intention of marrying him!
W-Wait a second, Mami-san!
What are you saying?
That Chizuru-san deceived all of us?
I don't know if it was "deceit."
But I think a year and a half is too long
to write off as an honest mistake.
At first, I jumped to
the wrong conclusion, too.
I thought Kazuya-san was in the wrong
for continuing to rent her out.
That Chizuru-san was just doing her job.
Don't think you can get off light after
wasting all those chances I gave you.
But I heard she lied to her own grandma,
and I didn't know what to think anymore.
This all scares me so much,
I'm even having trouble sleeping!
She takes money to hold hands,
get food together, and go on dates...
It ends now.
Behind that smile of hers, what in
the world is Mizuhara Chizuru thinking?
It's over for you,
Mizuhara Chizuru.
It's good to see you again.
That's a beautiful kimono.
I've been wanting to see you.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Room 301
Ichinose Sayuri
What? You want to know how much
Chizuru likes Kazuya-kun?
Sorry. They've been dating for 13 months,
two weeks, five days, and 11 hours.
That's quite precise
I thought I might ask her grandmother
how she feels about it all.
After all, my angel is too good
for that grandson of mine.
I still can't bring myself
to believe they're dating.
Please, Kazuya-kun is a lovely boy.
You can be proud of him.
You're the only one who
talks him up like that, Sayutaso.
But I'm sorry. My grandchild isn't one
to be up-front about how she feels.
I haven't heard anything from her.
How wise of her. Of course
Chizuru-san would be that refined.
Oh, no, she's just trying
too hard to be mysterious.
Her and her
high horse, gosh
She's like a
rom-com heroine
Enigmatic people are beautiful.
This is the first time she's ever
introduced me to her boyfriend, you know.
Oh, that's unusual in this day and age,
especially for a girl that pretty.
Not that I know what she's
been up to out of my sight.
She's very good at keeping secrets.
Oh, is she now?
Never mind me. It's not that big a deal.
Either way, I believe
in their future together.
I can see it when they're together...
The sight of them together, surrounded
by our families and their children.
squee
You don't say! Me, too!
Right?
The coast of happiness is never clear.
There are peaks and valleys,
and demons in your path,
a path you might even
lose sight of at times.
But whenever that happens, my late
husband gives me a kick in the behind.
"Don't stop believing.
Never stop believing," he'll say.
Just hearing that is all too reassuring!
Let's bring in your 88th on Mt. Asuka,
with the sakura in full bloom!
Yes, let's! I'm sure it'll
blow my illness away, too!
How many kids will they have?
Two or three?
What should we name them?
Th-That can't be.
It has to be some kind of mistake.
Chizuru-san would never
deceive us like that.
Right, Chizuru-san?
Hang on.
Wait a second.
Don't carry on like we're not here.
Chizuru-san isn't really
Kazuya's girlfriend?
There's no way.
I mean, they've always been together.
She stood up for Kazuya
during that boozer,
and in Shimoda, he risked
his life to save her.
Was all that an act, too?
And what's this about a ring? Is a rental
girlfriend allowed to accept that?
She even lied to her own grandma?
What the hell is all that about?
Hey, Kazuya! Say something!
Kibe...
What is even going on here?
Are you kidding me? Why is Mizuhara
being painted as the one in the wrong?
You know there's no way she could be!
Why'd Mami-chan have to be so misleading
after she assured me she wouldn't do this?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Kibe. Forgive me.
I don't care what you think of me.
But lay off Mizuhara!
You're wrong about her!
Why isn't Gran moving?
Why isn't she saying anything?
Is there any chance she believes
in Chizuru and lets this slide?
Hey, Kibe!
Please, no fighting!
Calm down, Yoshi!
Don't stop me, Kuri!
I just can't accept this!
You don't have a clue, Kazuya!
Nagomi-san was hospitalized
before this trip!
She was crestfallen she couldn't help
Chizuru-san after she lost Sayuri-san!
She was down in the dumps for a while!
But she kept it from you because
she didn't want Chizuru-san to know!
I had no idea...
She believed that you would
be the one to lift her spirits!
She trusted you and waited all this time!
I told you not to lie
to Nagomi-san, didn't I?!
So what's all this, you little punk?!
Pipe down, Yoshiaki.
You're bothering the staff.
But Nagomi-san! It was all a lie!
You were so sad...
Never mind me.
But...
I said, don't mind me!
I'll be fine. I can get over this.
Even if the first girlfriend my grandson
introduced to me was a rental,
even if the family's ring and our money
were used to fuel a mere dream,
even if I've learned that those words
and that smile were all a lie...
It was all too good to
be true to begin with.
One day, I'll look back and
laugh at my own foolishness.
Gran!
But the thing is, Chizuru-san...
Sayuri-san believed in you—
that her dear granddaughter introduced
a boyfriend to her for the first time.
And I'm sure she believed
it to her dying breath.
If what Mami-dono says is true,
then I can overlook anything but the
fact that you lied to my late friend.
I would like to believe
that this is all a mistake.
Is there anything you can
say in your defense?
There's nothing we can say!
Because we did lie!
I tried to, but she said
she was fine either way.
That if I wanted to talk, she'd listen,
but if I didn't, then she
didn't want to, either.
When she said that, I just couldn't
bring myself to tell her.
No! Mizuhara was torn up over it!
She just barely missed her
chance to tell the truth, is all!
But whatever we say now,
after lying for a year and a half,
it'll only sound like an excuse.
It's not fair!
I mean, Sayuri-san isn't here
to stand up for her.
There's nothing we can do anymore.
Hear me out, Mizuhara!
I'm not done here!
I...
But nobody in this world is a
better match for you than him.
I see.
Never mind.
We're done.
I'm tired now.
No...
You've got it all wrong, guys.
If you had to pick the worst declaration
of love in human history,
it'd have to be this moment here.
Before I knew it, that outpouring
of emotion had escaped my lips.
It was like charging into a gunfight
with nothing but a matchstick.
Mizuhara's not that kind of person.
This pathetic white knight's
final lie began to unfold.
Mizuhara did nothing wrong.
This is all my fault.
I don't care if people despise
me for this or beat me up.
But I swore I'd protect Mizuhara
Chizuru from any and all blame.
I could never bear to watch
such a nice girl,
a girl I love so much,
be painted in a horrible light!
So there's only one thing I can do now.
Next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Climax and Girlfriend."
"Climax and Girlfriend"